[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Why are you such a big deal?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "such", "a", "big", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "You must have a lot of Polish people --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "must", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "Polish", "people", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What does it mean to you to have that reputation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "you", "to", "have", "that", "reputation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, I've been really lucky to be at places where their brand helped me right away.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "really", "lucky", "to", "be", "at", "places", "where", "their", "brand", "helped", "me", "right", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Do you believe as a coach instinctively you can learn more from a loss than a victory?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "as", "a", "coach", "instinctively", "you", "can", "learn", "more", "from", "a", "loss", "than", "a", "victory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "I think you learn -- you learn from every experience, but a loss puts you in a position where you're more reflective, you can -- you go to deeper places than you do with a win.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "learn", "--", "you", "learn", "from", "every", "experience", ",", "but", "a", "loss", "puts", "you", "in", "a", "position", "where", "you", "'re", "more", "reflective", ",", "you", "can", "--", "you", "go", "to", "deeper", "places", "than", "you", "do", "with", "a", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Why do you think that happened in Athens, and what are you going to do to stop it happening in London when the whole world assumes you're going to win gold quite easily?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "that", "happened", "in", "Athens", ",", "and", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "to", "stop", "it", "happening", "in", "London", "when", "the", "whole", "world", "assumes", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "win", "gold", "quite", "easily", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, the very first thing is you don't go with assumptions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "very", "first", "thing", "is", "you", "do", "n't", "go", "with", "assumptions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Athens", "London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 88, "question": "How often do you think about that game?", "question_tokens": ["How", "often", "do", "you", "think", "about", "that", "game", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "I think about it often, because I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "about", "it", "often", ",", "because", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Hourly?", "question_tokens": ["Hourly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Not hourly.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "hourly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "How do you get it to gel and to work where they have to share that status?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "it", "to", "gel", "and", "to", "work", "where", "they", "have", "to", "share", "that", "status", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, the very first thing is you're honest with them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "very", "first", "thing", "is", "you", "'re", "honest", "with", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Why is ego now seen as a stick to beat people with?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "ego", "now", "seen", "as", "a", "stick", "to", "beat", "people", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "It's all part of the same thing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "part", "of", "the", "same", "thing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Is the American dream still as attainable as it was when you were young?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "American", "dream", "still", "as", "attainable", "as", "it", "was", "when", "you", "were", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Yes, I don't think it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "-- then how can we blame them?", "question_tokens": ["--", "then", "how", "can", "we", "blame", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, you know, it -- intellect does not know race, color, nationality, gender.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "--", "intellect", "does", "not", "know", "race", ",", "color", ",", "nationality", ",", "gender", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "CD", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What are the values that you like to instill in them, human values?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "values", "that", "you", "like", "to", "instill", "in", "them", ",", "human", "values", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "RZYZEWSKI: Well, the main thing is to be truthful, where you're honest with one another.", "answer_tokens": ["RZYZEWSKI", ":", "Well", ",", "the", "main", "thing", "is", "to", "be", "truthful", ",", "where", "you", "'re", "honest", "with", "one", "another", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paterno"]}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "It was a very sad thing, though, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "very", "sad", "thing", ",", "though", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "No, it was horrible, and I've respected Coach Paterno my entire life and had a chance to get to know him really well in the last year of his life.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "was", "horrible", ",", "and", "I", "'ve", "respected", "Coach", "Paterno", "my", "entire", "life", "and", "had", "a", "chance", "to", "get", "to", "know", "him", "really", "well", "in", "the", "last", "year", "of", "his", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What should Joe Paterno perhaps have done that he didn't?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "Joe", "Paterno", "perhaps", "have", "done", "that", "he", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, you should deal with it like -- like any team should deal with it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "should", "deal", "with", "it", "like", "--", "like", "any", "team", "should", "deal", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What does it take to be a champion in sports, and not just a winner, or a good sportsman, or even necessarily a great sportsman, but a champion over a long period of time?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "take", "to", "be", "a", "champion", "in", "sports", ",", "and", "not", "just", "a", "winner", ",", "or", "a", "good", "sportsman", ",", "or", "even", "necessarily", "a", "great", "sportsman", ",", "but", "a", "champion", "over", "a", "long", "period", "of", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, incredible commitment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "incredible", "commitment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What would that mean to you personally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "that", "mean", "to", "you", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I'll decide on that after it's over.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "decide", "on", "that", "after", "it", "'s", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What do you say to guys like that at that moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "guys", "like", "that", "at", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Yes, well, you keep it simple.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", ",", "you", "keep", "it", "simple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Do you think those guys in that moment understand that playing for their country beats anything else?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "those", "guys", "in", "that", "moment", "understand", "that", "playing", "for", "their", "country", "beats", "anything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Yes, they do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Do you even know how many you won?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "even", "know", "how", "many", "you", "won", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Eleven.", "answer_tokens": ["Eleven", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "In total, in your career and everything?", "question_tokens": ["In", "total", ",", "in", "your", "career", "and", "everything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "No, world championship, I know I have in the teens, but I'm not sure where.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "world", "championship", ",", "I", "know", "I", "have", "in", "the", "teens", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "where", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Is it just swimmer or athlete in total?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "just", "swimmer", "or", "athlete", "in", "total", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Female athlete, American.", "answer_tokens": ["Female", "athlete", ",", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Are you the female Michael Phelps or is he the male Natalie Coughlin?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "the", "female", "Michael", "Phelps", "or", "is", "he", "the", "male", "Natalie", "Coughlin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Oh, that's a really nice way to say that.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "really", "nice", "way", "to", "say", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Phelps", "Natalie Coughlin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Because when he stands there to dive in, he must want to kill everyone, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "when", "he", "stands", "there", "to", "dive", "in", ",", "he", "must", "want", "to", "kill", "everyone", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Isn't that what this is all about?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "what", "this", "is", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "We are competitive by nature.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "competitive", "by", "nature", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Before the race or during the race?", "question_tokens": ["Before", "the", "race", "or", "during", "the", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Just before it starts.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "before", "it", "starts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Are you nervous?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "nervous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I'm incredibly nervous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "incredibly", "nervous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "What is the swimmer's nightmare?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "swimmer", "'s", "nightmare", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "The swimmer's nightmare is not getting your suit on.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "swimmer", "'s", "nightmare", "is", "not", "getting", "your", "suit", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "What does it take to you to be an American competing in the Olympic games, which is watched by the whole world?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "take", "to", "you", "to", "be", "an", "American", "competing", "in", "the", "Olympic", "games", ",", "which", "is", "watched", "by", "the", "whole", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "It's pretty incredible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "incredible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Why were you so emotional?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "so", "emotional", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "It's an emotional event.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "emotional", "event", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Why continue?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "continue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I love the day to day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "the", "day", "to", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Being in your late 20s and being called old?", "question_tokens": ["Being", "in", "your", "late", "20s", "and", "being", "called", "old", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Could you even imagined just how well this has gone?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "even", "imagined", "just", "how", "well", "this", "has", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No, never.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]